One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Piece One Piece
‫ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس‬
Wano Arc Wano Arc Wano Arc
‫آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو آرك وانو‬
One Piece
‫ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس ون بيس‬
Oh, Inuarashi!
‫إينواراشي‬
Where have you been?
‫أين كنت؟‬
Something wrong, Kin'emon?
‫ما الخطب يا كينيمون؟‬
We're in a real predicament!
‫نواجه مشكلة كبيرة‬
Kin'emon and the Mink Musketeers An Abandoned Village Kuri
‫كينيمون وفرسان المينك قرية مهجورة في كوري‬
The enemy knows about the flyer and the moon tattoo?!
‫اكتشفوا أمر المنشورات ذات العلامة ووشم الهلال؟‬
That's right! It's all a big mess!
‫أجل، أصبحنا في فوضى‬
What do we do, Your Grace?!
‫ماذا نفعل أيها الدوق-ساما؟‬
We were distributing these covertly...
‫كنا نوزعها بشكل سري‬
I do not know how it leaked...
‫لا أعلم كيف تسرّب الخبر‬
We chose this coded symbol on the off chance it fell into the wrong hands.
‫كتبنا الرسالة على شكل رموز في حالة وقوعها في اليد الخطأ‬
But they've somehow uncovered the connection between this and the tattoo.
‫لكنهم يعرفون الرابط بين وشم الكاحل وهذا المنشور بطريقة ما‬
Right now in the capital...
‫وفي العاصمة الآن‬
Kaido and Orochi's underlings are apprehending our allies!
‫سر امرأة‬
A Woman's Secret
‫سمعتُ أنّ حلفاءنا يتعرضون للأسر على يد رجال كايدو وأوروتشي‬
– You're under arrest!
‫أنت رهن الاعتقال، أنت رهن الاعتقال‬
Stop resisting, rebel scum!
‫كفاك مقاومة أيها المتمرد‬
He had a flyer on him!
‫وجدت المنشور‬
Settle down!
‫اثبت مكانك‬
He's got the moon tattoo, too!
‫لديه وشم الهلال أيضًا‬
Anyone with that mark on their ankle is a rebel!
‫من يملك منهم العلامة على كاحله يُعد متمردًا‬
Report any you see!
‫أعلمونا في الحال إن رأيتموها‬
Word travels fast.
‫انتشرت الإشاعات بسرعة، يعرف الجميع في العاصمة بالأمر الآن‬
Patrolling bathhouses is just going to waste our time.
‫ليس علينا تضييع وقتنا في مراقبة الحمامات‬
How fortunate for you.
‫هنيئًا لك‬
What's that supposed to mean?
‫ماذا تقصد بذلك؟‬
That's Stealth Black for you...!
‫كما هو متوقع من ستيلث بلاك‬
I'll get him next time!
‫سأطيح به في المرة القادمة‬
You're just as culpable for letting them escape.
‫هذا لا يغير حقيقة أنك سمحت لهم بالهرب أيضًا‬
Oh, Komurasaki...!
‫كوموراساكي-دايو‬
Boss Kyoshiro...
‫الزعيم كيوشيرو‬
Komurasaki's wake has been canceled.
‫تمّ إلغاء مراسم نعي كوموراساكي‬
Things might get out of hand if this many grief-stricken people pour in.
‫قد تقع حادثة ما إن أتى عديد من المستائين من أمثالهم‬
A Pleasure Hall Flower Capital
‫منطقة ملذات في عاصمة الزهور‬
The funeral tomorrow will probably be even more crowded.
‫أعتقد أنّ الجنازة غدًا ستكون مزدحمة أكثر‬
May she rest in peace!
‫أدعو أن ترقد بسلام‬
Many are placing the blame for this upon your shoulders...
‫يضمر العديد الضغينة تجاهك‬
Please be careful.
‫لذلك كن حذرًا رجاءً‬
They should mind their own business.
‫إنهم لا يعرفون عمّ يتحدثون‬
There was no other way...
‫لم يكن هنالك خيار آخر‬
The one with the most to lose...
‫أكثر من يعاني من موتها هو أنا‬
Certainly.
‫بكل تأكيد‬
Lord Orochi is still in a foul mood.
‫أوروتشي-ساما غاضب‬
I'd wager this is the thorn in his side.
‫أعتقد أنّ هذا هو السبب‬
Ebisu Town
‫توقفا كلاكما‬
Stop it, you two!
‫بلدة إبيسو‬
Arguing won't resolve any of this!
‫لن يحلّ الجدال شيئًا‬
We're on the same side!
‫ألسنا رفاق؟‬
They're arresting everyone who sympathizes with our goal of eliminating Orochi...
‫يتعرّض حلفاؤنا الذين يريدون الإطاحة بأوروتشي للاعتقال واحدًا تلو الآخر‬
ever since your crew slipped up!
‫وذلك بسبب إخفاق طاقمك بلا شك‬
What was that?!
‫ماذا قلتِ؟‬
That little bear and his pals...
‫...ذلك الدب ورفاقه‬
must have told them the plan!
‫لا بدّ أنهم أخبروهم بخطتنا‬
Bepo and the others would rather die than talk! Don't underestimate them!
‫كان بيبو والبقية ليفضّلوا الموت على قول أي شيء‬
Wait! You're doing exactly what the enemy wants, Traf!
‫انتظر، هذا بالضبط ما يريده العدو يا تراو‬
Don't you tell me what to do, Black Leg!
‫لا تستطيع أن تملي عليّ ما أفعله أيها الساق السوداء-يا‬
Both of you, simmer down.
‫اهدآ كلاكما‬
You're the one who needs to cool your head!
‫ألست أنت من عليه أن يهدّئ أعصابه؟‬
You have to...
‫...عليكما أن‬
You have to trust each other!
‫عليكما أن تثقا ببعضكما‬
You're the most untrustworthy person I know!
‫أنت أكثر من لا يمكن الوثوق به‬
I didn't see a thing...
‫لكنني لم أرَ أي شيء‬
How'd your face end up like that after a few punches...?
‫كيف ضُربت حتى انتهى بك المطاف هكذا؟‬
Are you trying to run?!
‫هل تحاول الهرب؟‬
We need to eliminate those who were captured!
‫عليك تصفية من تمّ القبض عليهم‬
They must be silenced!
‫عليك إسكاتهم‬
What did you say?!
‫ماذا قلتِ؟‬
That is the way of the ninja world!
‫هذه هي طريقة النينجا‬
You're scary, Shinobu!
‫أنتِ مخيفة يا شينوبو‬
This isn't some game we're playing!
‫نحن لا نلعب هنا‬
We've been waiting twenty years for this moment!
‫كنا بانتظار هذه اللحظة طوال عشرين سنة‬
If we fail, we won't get another chance!
‫إن فشلنا الآن، لن نحصل على فرصة أخرى‬
That's enough, Shinobu!
‫توقفي يا شينوبو‬
Kan! My lord!
‫...كان-ساما‬
Things do not always go as planned!
‫لا تسير الأمور دائمًا كما نشتهي‬
I understand your frustration well...
‫أدرك إحباطك جيدًا‬
but it's a miracle we found allies whose goals aligned with our own!
‫لكن تحالفنا مع أشخاص مثلهم يشاركونا الغاية ذاتها لهو أمرٌ إعجازي بحد ذاته‬
Without them, Lord Oden's wish will never come to pass!
‫لا يمكننا تحقيق رغبة أودين-ساما إن خسرناهم‬
Pardon the intrusion! Pardon me!
‫معذرةً يا أهل الخير‬
I was outside and couldn't help but overhear!
‫سمعت أصواتكم من الخارج‬
You all have lovely voices!
‫ويا لها من أصوات عذبة‬
Hold it! Who are you?!
‫مهلًا، من تكون؟‬
Wow! What beauty! A goddess, no less!
‫كم أنت جميلة، هل أنت إلهة؟‬
Oh, you!
‫...أخجلتني‬
Please, come in.
‫تفضل بالدخول‬
Oh, thank you kindly.
‫أعتذر عن التطفل‬
Hey!
‫أوي‬
As I live and breathe...
‫...أيعقل أنكِ‬
Little Shinobu?!
‫شينوبو-تشان؟‬
Young Kanjuro!
‫كنجورو-كن‬
Then what I have is the genuine article, isn't it?!
‫هذا يعني أنّ هذه حقيقية‬
It's all anyone can talk about in the capital!
‫إنها حديث الجميع في العاصمة‬
I can't hold my excitement!
‫هذا يزيدني حماسة‬
Is it set to begin?! The great battle?!
‫هل حان وقت المعركة الحاسمة؟‬
The Northern Ringo Cemetery
‫المقبرة الشمالية في رينغو‬
My sword...
‫...سيفي‬
My sword!
‫سيفي‬
You're...
‫...أنتِ‬
You scared me!
‫لقد فاجأتني‬
Please, do not move...
‫لا تنهض بعد رجاءً‬
It will aggravate your wound...
‫سيتفاقم جرحك على هذا الحال‬
She's right! You don't need to get up yet!
‫صحيح، صحيح، ليس عليك أن تنهض بعد‬
Where am I?
‫أين أنا؟‬
You saved our lives earlier. Thank you so much.
‫شكرًا جزيلًا على إنقاذ حياتنا سابقًا‬
Thank you!
‫شكرًا لك‬
But in result, you were terribly wounded!
‫لقد أُصبت إصابة بليغة لأجلنا‬
I am truly... at a loss as to how to apologize.
‫لا أعرف كيف أقدم اعتذاري لك‬
It's my own fault I was hurt.
‫إصابتي هي بسبب قلة خبرتي‬
You have nothing to apologize for...
‫لا علاقة لكما بالأمر‬
Where'd that guy go?!
‫أين ذهب ذلك الرجل؟‬
He still has Shusui!
‫ما زال شوسوي معه‬
Please do not venture out with such an injury!
‫لا تفعل، لا يمكنك الذهاب وجرحك بليغ هكذا‬
That hurts!
‫مؤلم‬
That's my wounded side, you idiot!
‫الجرح في هذا الجانب أيتها الحمقاء‬
I'm so sorry!
‫ا-اعذرني‬
Honestly...!
‫...بحق‬
See ya!
‫إلى اللقاء‬
Do not go! Your wound has not yet healed!
‫لا تذهب، لم يشفى جرحك بعد‬
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
‫هذا مؤلم‬
I just told you that's my wounded arm! Pay attention!
‫قلت لكِ أنّ جرحي في هذا الجانب، ألا تفهمين؟‬
I-I am so sorry!
‫ا-اعذرني‬
Ow, ow, ow...
‫...مؤلم‬
It'll be okay, Mr. Samurai!
‫ستكون بخير أيها الساموراي-سان‬
You'll get better soon!
‫ستتحسن قريبًا‬
I stole this toad oil ointment in the capital...
‫...سرقت مرهم زيت الضفدع هذا من العاصمة‬
I mean, I bought it!
‫أعني أنني اشتريته‬
You stole it.
‫لقد سرقتِه‬
D-Did not.
‫بل اشتريته‬
Well, I don't care either way.
‫لا أهتم في كلتا الحالتين‬
This toad oil is amazing!
‫زيت الضفدع مذهل‬
Toad oil, huh? Well, I hope it works!
‫زيت ضفدع؟ أتمنى أن يفلح‬
Hey, Mr. Samurai!
‫بالمناسبة أيها الساموراي-سان‬
Don't leave us!
‫ابق معنا‬
Got something to eat?
‫ألديكما ما يؤكل؟‬
Yes! Would you like some now?!
‫أجل، أتريد بعضًا منه الآن؟‬
Gyukimaru?
‫غيوكيمارو؟‬
Th-That's right.
‫أ-أجل‬
The whole city is familiar with "Gyukimaru of Bandit's Bridge."
‫"يعرفه الجميع في العاصمة بـ"غيوكيمارو على جسر أويهاغي‬
The named blade Shusui has already been returned to where it belongs.
‫لقد أعدتُ السيف الشهير شوسوي إلى مكانه الأصلي‬
It's a treasure that was stolen from the grave of the legendary samurai of Wano, Ryuma!
‫ذلك السيف سُرق من قبر ساموراي أسطوري في بلاد وانو يُدعى ريوما‬
It's unknown where he resides,
‫لا أعرف أين يعيش‬
but he'll confront any armed individual who attempts to cross the bridge.
‫لكن المحارب الراهب يظهر نفسه كلما حاول شخص مسلح عبور الجسر‬
Ah, so he's always there? No need to rush then...
‫هو دائمًا ما يكون هناك؟ لا داعي للعجلة إذًا‬
I'm still curious about Gyukimaru,
‫أتساءل من يكون غيوكيمارو هذا‬
but first, who are you two?
‫لكن من تكونان أنتما أولا؟‬
Why was that grim reaper- looking guy after you?
‫كان حاصد الأرواح ذاك يسعى خلفكما‬
It's because we incurred the wrath of the shogun of Wano.
‫المسألة هي أننا أغضبنا شوغن بلاد وانو‬
The shogun, huh?
‫الشوغن؟‬
Oro... Oroshi?
‫أورو... أوروشي؟‬
It's Orochi.
‫اسمه أوروتشي‬
Hey, Mr. Samurai!
‫اسمع أيها الساموراي-سان‬
My name is Toko!
‫اسمي توكو‬
TOKO
‫توكو‬
If you use the "O" honorific, you get "Otoko," and that means "man."
‫إن أضفت "أو" التشريف قبله تصبح أوتوكو، ولكنني لستُ ذكرًا‬
O
‫أو‬
It's funny, right?!
‫أليس هذا مضحكًا؟‬
No, not really.
‫ليس تمامًا‬
Everyone says it's funny! Why don't you think so?!
‫يجد الجميع هذا مضحكًا، فما خطبك أنت؟‬
Beats me.
‫لا أعلم‬
Though you wear the garb of a Wanese samurai,
‫على أنك ترتدي ملابس ساموراي من بلاد وانو إلا أنك من خارجها، صحيح؟‬
You don't look like a bad...
‫...لا أراك شخصًا سـ‬
A bad per...
‫...شخصًا سيـ‬
A bad person.
‫شخصًا سيئًا‬
Just say it!
‫قوليها دون تردد‬
I apologize!
‫اعذرني‬
Mr. Samurai, you're pretty scary!
‫أنت مخيف أيها الساموراي-سان‬
But you're a really nice person because you saved us!
‫لكنك شخص لطيف لأنك أنقذت حياتنا‬
Um...
‫...المعذرة‬
I wish to tell you a secret, but you must promise to keep it.
‫أود أن أخبرك بسر، لكن يجب أن تصونه‬
What is it?
‫ما هو؟‬
I'm... looking for my older brother.
‫أنا أبحث عن أخي الكبير‬
We were separated twenty years ago...
‫انفصلنا عن بعضنا قبل عشرين سنة‬
And now, I think he might be in Wano!
‫وأظن أنه في بلاد وانو الآن‬
His name is...
‫...اسم أخي هو‬
Kozuki Momonosuke.
‫كوزكي مومونوسكي‬
I'm his younger sister.
‫أنا أخته‬
My name is Hiyori!
‫واسمي هيوري‬
Momonosuke's younger sister?!
‫أنتِ أخت مومونوسكي؟‬
I knew it!
‫توقعت ذلك‬
I'm so glad I summoned the courage to tell you!
‫أنا سعيدة لأنني استجمعت شجاعتي وقلتها‬
I kind of took a chance.
‫كانت مجازفة كبيرة‬
You do know my brother, don't you?!
‫أنت تعرف أخي، أليس كذلك؟‬
And he is okay, right?!
‫وهو بخير، صحيح؟‬
Wait! Calm down!
‫مهلًا، اهدئي‬
I need to collect my thoughts.
‫عليّ ترتيب أفكاري‬
Lately, rumors abound concerning the return of the Kozuki Clan.
‫هنالك إشاعات هذه الأيام عن عودة عشيرة الكوزكي‬
Coincidentally, a strong, kindhearted samurai from overseas is here.
‫وفي نفس الوقت، يوجد هنا ساموراي قوي ولطيف من خارج البلاد‬
I thought he might be my brother's ally!
‫لذلك فكرت أنه قد يكون حليف أخي‬
Or are you an enemy trying to track him down?!
‫أم أنك عدو يسعى خلف أخي؟‬
I'm his ally.
‫أنا حليفه‬
I'm definitely his ally.
‫لا تقلقي، أنا حليفه‬
I am so relieved.
‫هذا مطمئن‬
Do you know if Kin'emon is alive?
‫أتعلم إن كان كينيمون لا يزال حيًّا؟‬
Are Kanjuro, Raizo, and Kikunojo all with him?
‫هل كنجورو ورايزو وكيكونوجو معه جميعًا؟‬
Kikunojo?
‫كيكونوجو؟‬
Oh, you mean Kiku?
‫تقصدين كيكو؟‬
Yeah, but wait... Something doesn't add up.
‫أجل، لكن مهلًا، هنالك أمر يشغلني‬
Are you really Momo's sister?
‫هل أنتِ أخت مومو حقًّا؟‬
Let me explain.
‫دعني أشرح الأمر‬
I see.
‫فهمت‬
That's right.
‫هذا صحيح‬
Momo from twenty years ago appears to be eight years old,
‫مومو القادم من عشرين سنة مضت يبدو في الثامنة من عمره‬
and you're supposed to be his younger sister,
‫يُفترض أن تكوني أخته الصغرى لكنكِ كبرتِ خلال هذه السنوات العشرين فصار عمرك 26‬
Yes.
‫أجل‬
By the way...
‫بالمناسبة‬
...is it okay for her to hear all of this?
‫ألا بأس أن تستمع لكل هذا؟‬
It's okay because I already knew!
‫لا بأس، لأنني أعرف ذلك مسبقًا‬
It was a secret between Big Sis and me!
‫كان ذلك سرًّا بين أختي الكبيرة وبيني‬
Otoko is one of the few close friends who knows my true identity.
‫أوتوكو واحدة من أصحابي المقربين الذين يعرفون هويتي الحقيقية‬
Her cheerfulness sustains me day-to-day...
‫إنّ بهجتها تساندني كل يوم‬
Twenty years ago, I was still a little girl like her...
‫قبل عشرين سنة، كنت لا أزال طفلة صغيرة مثلها‬
but I will never forget what happened that day.
‫لكنني لن أنسى أبدًا ما حدث ذلك اليوم‬
You must escape... to the future!
‫عليكم المغادرة إلى المستقبل‬
Mother, please don't do this!
‫أرجوكِ توقفي يا أمي‬
Mother! Mother!
‫أمي، أمي‬
I couldn't make sense of anything that was happening.
‫لم أكن أفهم ما يحدث وكنت مرتبكة‬
In the blazing fire,
‫...ووسط النيران الملتهبة‬
my brother and the others disappeared right before my eyes...
‫اختفى أخي والبقية أمام ناظريّ تمامًا‬
It was the same day I lost my father Oden,
‫فقدتُ والدي أودين في نفس اليوم‬
and even my mother...
‫وفقدتُ والدتي أيضًا‬
In a single day, I suddenly lost everything.
‫في ذلك اليوم، فقدت كل شيء فجأة‬
I was told my brother would return in twenty years...
‫قيل لي أنّ أخي سيعود بعد عشرين سنة‬
but for something so uncertain, my hope was fleeting...
‫لكن لم أستطع التشبث بأمل غير مؤكد كهذا‬
I did not have the will to go on for all those years.
‫لم أكن أملك الإرادة لأعيش كل تلك السنين‬
Why didn't you travel through time too?
‫لماذا لم ينقلوكِ عبر الزمن كالبقية؟‬
In case something happened either to my brother or to me...
‫في حال أصابني أو أخي مكروه‬
they did not want the Kozuki bloodline to end.
‫كانوا حريصين على ألّا ينتهي نسل الكوزكي‬
That's too cruel...
‫يا له من مصير قاسٍ‬
But my father's retainer,
‫...لكن أحد خدّام والدي‬
Kawamatsu the Kappa, provided emotional support and raised me with patience.
‫يدعى كاواماتسو الكابا، رباني ودعمني عاطفيًّا‬ ‫كابا = مخلوق في الأساطير اليابانية يعيش في الأنهار ويصطاد السمك‬
A kappa?!
‫كابا؟‬
Indeed.
‫أجل‬
It is hard to believe such creatures exist, but he takes great pride in being one.
‫يصعب تصديق أنّ تلك المخلوقات موجودة، لكنه فخور جدًّا بكونه منها‬
On the day that the castle burned, we were surrounded by the enemy,
‫في اليوم الذي احترقت فيه القلعة، كنا محاصرين من طرف العدو‬
but we escaped undetected through a drainage channel in the moat.
‫لكننا هربنا عبر الخندق إلى قنوات التصريف دون أن تتم ملاحظتنا‬
Princess! I ask for patience!
‫تماسكي يا أميرتي رجاءً‬
After losing my father, mother, and brother,
‫بعد خسارتي لوالدي ووالدتي وأخي‬
I couldn't speak from the shock of it all, but he was always upbeat and supportive.
‫فقدت صوتي من أثر الصدمة، لكنه كان متفائلًا وداعمًا لي دائمًا‬
Princess! This is the Kappa Dance!
‫يا أميرتي، هذه رقصة الكابا‬
♪ Come on! Kappappa, kappappa, ♪ ♪ kappappa and pa! ♪
‫هيا، كابابا، كابابا، كابابا وبا‬
♪ Kappappa, kappappa... ♪
‫كابابا، كابابا‬
Kawamatsu, you're hungry too, aren't you?
‫أنت جائع أيضًا يا كاواماتسو؟‬
No, my tummy's upset. That's why it's growling.
‫كلا، أنا مصاب بعسر هضم طفيف، لهذا تصدر معدتي أصواتًا‬
Please... Please eat at least half.
‫رجاءً... رجاءً كل نصفه‬
No, I'm fine. I found a grilled fish swimming in the river earlier.
‫لا، لا، لقد وجدت سمكة مشوية في النهر قبل قليل‬
A grilled fish in the river?
‫سمكة مشوية في النهر؟‬
That's right!
‫صحيح‬
So I filleted it real quick and ate it on the way.
‫قطعتها وأكلها‬
He did not eat much himself, but he did his best to feed me.
‫لم يكن يأكل الكثير، لكنه كان يحاول إطعامي‬
Due to the kindness of my dutiful protector, Kawamatsu,
‫وبفضل لطف كاواماتسو الذي حماني من أعماق روحه‬
I gradually learned to laugh again.
‫بدأت أضحك تدريجيًّا‬
Where's this guy now?
‫وأين هو الآن؟‬
I think when I was about thirteen,
‫عندما كنت في عمر يناهز الثلاثة عشر‬
we were separated...
‫انفصلنا عن بعضنا‬
But Kawamatsu is a strong samurai,
‫لكن كاواماتسو ساموراي قوي‬
so he must still be out there, awaiting the day of the great battle!
‫واثقة أنه ينتظر يوم المعركة النهائية في بقعةٍ في بلادنا‬
How I wish to see him and the others again...
‫كم أودّ رؤيته ورؤية البقية‬
I wanna see a kappa too!
‫أريد رؤية كابا أيضًا يا أختاه‬
Zorojuro...
‫زوروجورو-سان‬
Who else is preparing for the great battle?
‫من غيرك أيضًا يستعد للمعركة النهائية؟‬
Well, let's see...
‫...لنرَ‬
Then Doggy and Kitty are preparing too?!
‫الكلب-تشان والقط-تشان موجودان أيضًا؟‬
Yeah.
‫أجل‬
I heard that they were both dead, so I thought I would never see them again!
‫سمعت أنهما ماتا، لذلك لم أتوقع رؤيتهما مجددًا‬
Nekomamushi might not be in Wano yet...
‫ربما لم يصل نيكوماموشي إلى بلاد وانو بعد‬
What are you doing?
‫ماذا تفعلين؟‬
I am so, so happy...
‫...أنا جدًّا، جدًّا سعيدة‬
You crack me up, Big Sis!
‫أنتِ مضحكة يا أختاه‬
But I will not cry!
‫لكنني لن أبكي‬
I am the daughter of a samurai!
‫لأنني ابنة ساموراي‬
If Doggy and Kitty will be there,
‫إن كان الكلب-تشان والقط-تشان سيشاركان أيضًا‬
then it's possible the entirety of the Nine Red Scabbards will assemble!
‫من الممكن أنّ يجتمع جميع الأغماد التسعة‬
I'm not so sure of that.
‫لست متأكدًا من ذلك‬
Kin'emon.
‫كينيمون‬
Kanjuro.
‫كنجورو‬
Raizo.
‫رايزو‬
Okiku.
‫أوكيكو‬
Inuarashi.
‫إينواراشي‬
Nekomamushi.
‫نيكوماموشي‬
THE NINE RED SCABBARDS
‫الأغماد التسعة‬
All we know is those six and Momonosuke.
‫كل من نعرف بشأنهم هم هؤلاء الستة ومومونوسكي‬
We haven't met the last three yet.
‫لكننا لم نلتق بالثلاثة الآخرين بعد‬
I spoke of the first of those three, Kawamatsu,
‫الثلاثة الآخرين هم كاواماتسو الذي أخبرتك عنه‬
KAWAMATSU
‫كاواماتسو‬
DENJIRO
‫دنجيرو‬
ASHURA DOJI
‫أشورا دوجي‬
and there's Denjiro and Ashura Doji.
‫ودنجيرو وأشورا دوجي‬
I do not know where they are or if they are safe...
‫لا أعلم أين هم أو ما إن كانوا سالمين‬
But now, with everyone in the capital in an uproar about this flyer...
‫لكن الجميع يتحدثون عن هذه المنشورات في العاصمة‬
I just know they will appear!
‫متأكدة أنهم سيأتون‬
Is that the flyer we handed out to the rebels?
‫هل هذا من المنشورات التي سلمناها للحلفاء المحتملين؟‬
Yes.
‫أجل‬
Thanks to that uproar, the message has spread very fast, which you'd think is a good thing,
‫بفضل الجلبة، انتشرت المعلومات بسرعة، وقد يكون هذا جيدًا‬
but it actually puts us in a tight spot...
‫ولكن في الواقع هذا لا يصبّ صالحنا‬
seeing as the rendezvous point was compromised and our allies caught.
‫مكان اللقاء سُرّب ورفاقنا أسروا‬
Things are looking a bit dicey.
‫بدأ الأمر يصبح مقلقًا‬
It will be all right.
‫سيكون كل شيء بخير‬
That is my belief.
‫أنا أؤمن بذلك‬
Well...
‫...حسنًا‬
Too many captains sink the ship. I'm gonna stop fretting.
‫كثرة القباطنة على سفينة واحدة قد يغرقها، لذا لن أُقلق بالي‬
Oh, yes! Certainly!
‫هذا صحيح‬
Before anything else, I want you to get well!
‫عليك أن تتحسن قبل كل شيء‬
Now, get some rest.
‫والآن خذ قسطًا من الراحة‬
Yeah, you don't have to tell me twice...
‫أجل، ليس عليكِ إخباري بذلك‬
Otoko, this is miracle!
‫أوتوكو، هذه معجزة‬
I am overjoyed!
‫أنا سعيدة‬
My brother is alive!
‫أخي حي‬
I'm happy for you, Big Sis!
‫أنا سعيدة من أجلك يا أختاه‬
Toko, this is great!
‫توكو، أنا سعيدة‬
Can't they keep it down? So much for sleeping!
‫ألن يخرسا؟ كيف سأنام هكذا؟‬
But he is only eight!
‫لكنه في الثامنة من عمره‬
How peculiar.
‫لكم هذا غريب‬
My brother is still a child.
‫لا يزال أخي طفلًا‬
I suppose Kin'emon and the others haven't changed in twenty years either.
‫أعتقد أنّ كينيمون والبقية لم يتغيروا عمّا كانوا عليه قبل عشرين سنة أيضًا‬
I cannot help but wonder how our reunion will be.
‫أتساءل كيف سيكون لقاؤنا‬
Perhaps it is better not to see them before the great battle.
‫ربما من الأفضل ألّا أراهم قبل المعركة النهائية‬
I should not interfere in a samurai's struggle.
‫قد يضعف وجودي من عزم الساموراي‬
Agreed, Otoko?
‫أليس كذلك يا أوتوكو؟‬
LOWER CAPITAL
‫عاصمة الزهور‬
Rasetsu Town Flower Capital
‫بلدة راسيتسو عاصمة الزهور‬
PRISON
‫سجن‬
RASETSU            PRISON
‫سجن راسيتسو‬
Prisoners' Quarters AKA the Public Cells Rasetsu Town
‫زنزانات علنية معقل سجناء بلدة راسيتسو‬
I didn't they'd have caught so many ruffians!
‫لم أتوقع رؤية هذا العدد من المجرمين‬
People, take a good, long look at them!
‫أيها الشعب، أمعنوا النظر إليهم‬
Get your ass in there already!
‫هيا ادخل بسرعة‬
Too bad for you.
‫يا لسوء حظكم‬
You've been outed, your scheme revealed!
‫كُشف عن خطتكم سلفًا‬
You have failed.
‫لقد فشلتم‬
Sir Fukurokuju, please wait!
‫انتظر يا فوكوروكوجو‬
What would lead you believe that this ankle tattoo marks us as rebels?!
‫ما الذي يجعلك تعتقد أنّ وشم الكاحل هو علامة للتمرد؟‬
This is just a popular design! We have nothing to do with any kind of rebellion!
‫إنه مجرد تصميم شائع، لا علاقة لنا بأي تمرد‬
Enough! What's your explanation for this flyer, then?!
‫صمتًا، كيف تفسّر هذا المنشور إذًا؟‬
With the reversed crescent moon at its center?
‫الهلال المعكوس في منتصف المنشور‬
A sign of rebellion against Shogun Orochi, perhaps?
‫لربما هي علامة تشير إلى تمرد ضد أوروتشي-ساما؟‬
It's a dead ringer for your tattoos.
‫إنه يبدو مثل وشمكم تمامًا‬
Shogun Orochi is the one giving the order, so sit down and shut up!
‫هذا أمر من أوروتشي-ساما، لذا اخرسوا والزموا أماكنكم‬
We're in a serious jam...
‫نحن في ورطة‬
Will everyone think...
‫...هل سيعتقد الجميع‬
that we blabbed about the plan?
‫أننا من فضح لهم بالخطة؟‬
Don't worry...
‫...لا تقلقا‬
Captain will continue to believe in us...
‫أنا واثق أنّ القبطان سيصدقنا‬
Prisoner Mining Camp Udon
‫منجم سجناء أودون‬
Come on, come on! Wipe the floor with them already!
‫هيا، أوسعوهما ضربًا‬
I wish I could join a sumo match too...
‫أريد الانضمام لنزال السومو أيضًا‬
I'm Madilloman! A Gifter who ate the Armadillo SMILE Fruit!
‫أنا ماديلومان، غيفتر مستخدم لفاكهة أرماديلو‬
Madilloman A Gifter Armadillo SMILE Fruit
‫ماديلومان غيفتر - مستخدم فاكهة سمايل أرماديلو‬
Oh, you look like you have tough body!
‫يبدو جسدك صلب‬
Perfect for my training!
‫مثالي لتدريبي‬
You moron!
‫أيها الأحمق‬
I'm rockin' seastone bullets in these bad boys!
‫الرصاصات المحشوة في هذا السلاح مصنوعة من الحجر البحري‬
You're finished, fellas!
‫انتهى أمركما‬
They're "finished"?
‫انتهى أمرهما؟‬
How blind are these idiots?! It's far from "finished."
‫لِمَ لم يدركوا الأمر بعد؟ لم ينتهِ أمرهما على الإطلاق‬
Gramps!
‫أيها العجوز‬
Go right, duck, and then jump.
‫اذهب يمينًا ثمّ اجلس مقرفصًا ثمّ اقفز‬
Get dead!
‫فلتمت‬
Run!
‫اركض‬
Okay!
‫حاضر‬
"Go right"!
‫أذهب يمينًا‬
"Duck"!
‫أجلس مُقرفصًا‬
And...
‫...وبعدها‬
You little...!
‫أيها‬
..."jump"!
‫أقفز‬
Ow, ow, ow...
‫مؤلم‬
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn, damn!
‫سحقًا، سحقًا، سحقًا، سحقًا، سحقًا‬
Good job, gramps! Keep it up!
‫أحسنت عملًا أيها العجوز، واصل ذلك‬
What the...?! Are you able to peek into the future?
‫كيف ذلك؟ أيمكنك رؤية المستقبل أو ما شابه؟‬
Screw you!
‫لا تعبث معي‬
That's pure nonsense! What'd you actually do?!
‫هذا محال، ما الذي فعلته أيها اللعين؟‬
Gramps! Go left next!
‫أيها العجوز، اذهب تاليًا يسارًا‬
Why, you...!
‫...نلت منك أيها‬
"Left"!
‫يسارًا‬
Dammit, that geezer!
‫سحقًا لذلك العجوز‬
Try this on for size!
‫خذ هذه‬
"Left"! "Left"! "Left"! "Left"!
‫يسارًا، يسارًا، يسارًا، يسارًا‬
You little cheat!
‫أيها الوغد‬
Bull's-eye!
‫نلت منك‬
Guns can't take me down!
‫لا يمكن الإطاحة بي بالأسلحة النارية‬
Y-You sneaky little...!
‫أ-أيها الوغد‬
It's not over yet!
‫ليس لدي خيار آخر‬
That's not it.
‫ليس هو‬
That's just the normal armament...
‫هذا هاكي تسلح عادي‬
Oh, crap!
‫سحقًا‬
Armadi-Guard!
‫أرمادي غارد‬ ‫دفاع المدرع‬
This isn't it...
‫هذا ليس هو‬
This is still just the normal armament...
‫هذا مجرد هاكي تسلح عادي‬
Huh?! Weren't you gonna hit me?!
‫ماذا؟ ألن تضربني؟‬
Alpaca Fencing!
‫ألباكا كينبو‬ ‫أسلوب قتال الألباكا‬
Hey! Which way next?!
‫...أوي، أين يجب أن أذهب تاليًا‬
Sir Straw Hat!
‫يا فتى قبعة القش؟‬
Alright! Stop right there!
‫حسنًا، توقف مكانك‬
It'll be easier this way!
‫سيكون الأمر أسهل هكذا‬
I'm so sorry...!
‫المعذرة‬
Ready when you are, Alpacaman!
‫لنقم بهذا يا ألباكامان‬
Bring it!
‫أجل‬
Put me down! It's not right for me to burden you this way!
‫ضعني أرضًا، لا أريد التسبب لك بمزيدٍ من المشكلات‬
Nope. Actually, the heavier the better.
‫كلا، كلما كان الوزن أثقل كان أفضل‬
It's good for my training!
‫من أجل تدريبي‬
I see, I see...!
‫فهمت الأمر‬
This flyer told us all we needed to know of the upcoming battle!
‫عرفنا بأمر المعركة النهائية عن طريق هذه المنشورات‬
Two birds on fire... That means twilight on the day of the Fire Festival!
‫طائران ناريّان"، هذا يعني عند طلوع الشفق في يوم مهرجان النار"‬
The rendezvous point for the raid is Habu Port!
‫ومكان اللقاء للغارة هو ميناء هابو‬
Young Kin'emon must've put his brain into overtime for this.
‫لا بدّ أنّ كينيمون-كن فكر كثيرًا في هذا‬
Young... Kin'emon?
‫كينيمون... -كن؟‬
Oh, why are you giving me that look,
‫...لماذا تنظرين إلي هكذا‬
Little Shinobu?!
‫يا شينوبو-تشان؟‬
So, that's how things are. The dejected looks on your faces make total sense.
‫لا عجب أنّ وجهك تعلوه نظرة كئيبة‬
The plan's as good as ruined,
‫لقد فشلت الخطة‬
what with our enemies aware of it.
‫أمسى العدو على عِلم بها‬
Mm-hmm. That is correct...
‫نعم، هذا صحيح‬
Allies who bear the reversed crescent moon tattoo—the sign of our rebellion—
‫حلفاؤنا ذوو وشم الهلال المعكوس الذي يرمز للثورة يؤسرون واحدًا تلو الآخر‬
If only there was some way to take it back and tell them, "It was all fake!"
‫ليت هنالك طريقة نجعلهم يظنون أنّ هذه الخطة مزيفة لنكملها‬
But that would mislead your allies as well.
‫لكن ذلك سيربك حلفاءكم أيضًا‬
Before this, however, I didn't know about the crescent moon ankle tattoo.
‫ولكن لم أكن أعلم بوشم الهلال المعكوس‬
It brought in allies like myself.
‫لذا لقد تمكنتم من ضمان حلفاء آخرين مثلي‬
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
‫ليس هو، لا يمكنني فعلها بشكل صحيح‬
This whole time, when you hit a foe you say, "That wasn't it"!
‫في كل مرة تضرب فيها أحدهم تقول "ليس هو" مرارًا وتكرارًا‬
What are you trying to do?
‫ما الذي تحاول فعله؟‬
I wanna send enemies flying with a punch that doesn't even touch them!
‫أريد تسديد لكمة تُرسل الأعداء محلّقين دون لمسهم‬
If I do that...
‫...بتلك الطريقة‬
I think I can break through Kaido's tough scales!
‫أظنني أستطيع اختراق حراشف كايدو القاسية‬
Send enemies flying with a punch that doesn't touch...
‫لكمة ترسل الأعداء محلّقين دون لمسهم؟‬
Yeah. I won't know if it works until I actually do it.
‫أجل، لن أعلم إن كانت ستنجح ما لم أجربها‬
The thing is, I've seen it before...
‫لكنني رأيت ذلك من قبل‬
Both Rayleigh...
‫...ريلي‬
and that battle-axe guy...
‫وصاحب الفأس‬
used the same armament haki.
‫كِلاهما استعملا نفس هاكي التسلح‬
How is theirs different from mine?!
‫أين يكمن الاختلاف بيني وبينهما؟‬
Haki must be a foreign concept.
‫لا بدّ أنّ هذا الهاكي مفهوم أجنبي‬
You know something?!
‫هل تعرف شيئًا؟‬
In Wano, we utilize an invisible power that stems from the body and covers one's blade.
‫في بلاد وانو، هنالك مفهوم قوة يغطّي سيوفنا انطلاقًا من أجسادنا‬
A good sword will cut even iron when you need it to,
‫بإمكان السيف الجيد قطع الحديد إن أردنا منه ذلك‬
and when you don't, it won't even nick a sheet of paper.
‫لكن إن لم نرد، فلن يقطع حتى ورقة‬
It's at the swordsman's discretion!
‫الأمر منوط بالسيّاف‬
Gramps...!
‫أيها العجوز‬
Check out this geezer! Ready for us to end you?!
‫أيها الأحمق، هل تتقدم لتنال حتفك؟‬
Sir Straw Hat.
‫يا فتى قبعة القش‬
Watch as I demonstrate the power honed through my days of sword fighting.
‫راقب المهارة التي اعتدتُ صقلها عبر نزالات السيافة‬
Despite being the centerpiece of a sick execution game,
‫رغم أنه وسط عرض قتالي مميت‬
he's using it as a training opportunity?!
‫إلا أنّ هذا الرجل يدرب نفسه؟‬
Sir Straw Hat! Give me directions!
‫يا فتى قبعة القش، أرشدني‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
He'll swing down his right sword, full force!
‫سيلوّح بسيفه الأيمن بكل قوته‬
I got it!
‫مفهوم‬
Damn you, geezer!
‫أيها العجوز اللعين‬
He knocked him back!
‫أطاح به‬
Gramps...
‫...أيها العجوز‬
Old man Hyo dropped that Gifter!
‫أطاح العجوز هيو بأحد الغيفترز‬
Alpacaman!
‫ألباكامان‬
That old weakling... I swear he had one foot in the grave.
‫ذلك العجوز الخرف، ظننت أنه على شفير الموت‬
But he's surprisingly spry!
‫لكن يبدو أنه ما زال يتمتع ببعض الشباب‬
Could old man Hyo actually be
‫...أيعقل أن يكون العجوز هيو‬
the renowned Hyogoro the Flower?!
‫هو هيوغورو الزهرة المشهور؟‬
Sir Straw Hat...
‫...يا فتى قبعة القش‬
if this is something that you are striving to accomplish,
‫إن كان هذا أمر تريد انجازه‬
perhaps I can be of some assistance.
‫ربما أستطيع مساعدتك قليلًا‬
You gotta teach me!
‫علمني‬
That's exactly it!
‫ذلك ما كنت أسعى إليه‬